Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Thank You Letters, 1969-1972 (Box 209, Folder 3-4)
- Thurston, J.W., Gen, Chairman, NYC, 1930-1965 (Box 209, Folder 5)
- Train Length Bill, 1934-1938 (Box 209, Folder 6)
- Transportation Act of 1939-40 (Box 209, Folder 7)
- Transportation Comm., Sen Speno, 1969 (Box 209, Folder 8)
- Transportation Dept. of - Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 209, Folder 9)
- TPEL Correspondence, UTU, 1969-1970 (Box 209, Folder 10)
- Truck Train Legislation, 1968-1969 (Box 209, Folder 11-12)
- Turbotrain, 1969 (Box 209, Folder 13)
- T.V. Debate, and Hiltz, 1963 (Box 209, Folder 14)
- Unification Legislative Boards, 1969-1970 (Box 209, Folder 15)
- Union-Label Service Trades, 1965-1968 (Box 209, Folder 16)
- U.S. Senator - Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box 209, Folder 17)
- United Railroad Operating Crafts (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Weekly Pay Bill, 1930-1962 (Box 210, Folder 2-3)
- Work Rules Dispute, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 210, Folder 4)
- Y Selkirk Situation, 1968-1970 (Box 210, Folder 5)
- Y.M.C.A. Railroad, Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 210, Folder 6)
- Youth and Work Council, Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 210, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1942-1943 (Box 210, Folder 8)
- B&A Railroad (Box 211, Folder 1-2)
- Boston and Maine Railroad (Box 211, Folder 5-6)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad (Box 211, Folder 7-9)
- Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal (Box 211, Folder 10)
- Bush Terminal (Box 211, Folder 11)
- Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburg Railroad (Box 211, Folder 12-13)
- Buffalo Creek Railroad (Box 211, Folder 14)
- Central New England (Box 211, Folder 15)
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad (Box 211, Folder 16-32)
- Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad (Box 212, Folder 1-11)
- Erie Railroad (Box 212, Folder 12-17)
- Erie Railroad (Box 213, Folder 1-13)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad (Box 214, Folder 1-7)
- Long Island Railroad (Box 214, Folder 8-13)
- New Haven Railroad (Box 214, Folder 14)
- New York Central Railroad (Box 214, Folder 15-17)
- New York Central Railroad (Box 215, Folder 1-33)
- New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad (Box 216, Folder 1)
- New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad (Box 216, Folder 2-3)
- New York, Ontario and Western Railroad (Box 216, Folder 4)
- Nickel Plate Railroad (Box 216, Folder 5)
- Norfolk and Western Railroad (Box 216, Folder 6-7)
- Penn Central Railroad (Box 216, Folder 8-18)
- Prattsburgh Railroad (Box 216, Folder 19)
- Rutland Railroad (Box 216, Folder 20)
- Southern Railroad (Box 216, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Railroad Documentation (Box 216, Folder 22-26)
- Generally re Full Crew Case Files, 1920-1969 (Box 217, Folder 1)
- Generally re Full Crew Case Files, 1920-1969 (Box 218, Folder 1)
- Generally re Full Crew Case Files, 1920-1969 (Box 219, Folder 1)
- Generally re Full Crew Case Files, 1920-1969 (Box 220, Folder 1)
- Generally re Full Crew Case Files, 1920-1969 (Box 221, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Documents - Includes correspondence, clippings, Scrapbook,, 1935-39 Expense Book (Box 222, Folder 1)
- Publications - Includes Lists of Delegates booklets; examination booklets, "News Gram", 1962-69; agreements; convention proceedings, "NYS Democratic Yearbook," 1958, 1959; and other miscellaneous publications (Box 223, Folder 1)
- EUMA Educational Program, 1961 (Box 224, Folder 15)
- Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 2)
- Second Annual Labor Institute, 1958 (Box 224, Folder 3)
- B of RT: B of LF & E -- Joint Education Course (Box 224, Folder 4)
- New York's New Era of Progress: 1959 Yearbook (Box 224, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen: Legislative and Educational Activities (Box 224, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers - Education Program: General Committee of Adjustment, New York Central System, Lines East, 1963 (Box 224, Folder 7)
- B of LF & E: Home Study Courses (Box 224, Folder 8)
- Publications (Box 224, Folder 9)
- To Provide Full Crews on Trains in Interstate Commerce: Hearings, 1935 (Box 224, Folder 10)
- Rock-Quarious Or: I Am Serious [Fella], 1970 (Box 224, Folder 11)
- B of RT: B of LF & E -- Lake Texoma - Joint Summer Educational Course (Box 224, Folder 12)
- 37th Convention Education Program, 1959 (Box 224, Folder 14)
- Publications (Box 224, Folder 28)
- Compulsory Arbitration in the Railroad Work Rules Dispute (Box 224, Folder 16)
- B of LF & E - Legislative and Educational Activities (Box 224, Folder 17)
- New York State Legislative and Education Board - B of LF & E, 1967 (Box 224, Folder 18)
- Sworn statement of Mr. Albert William Faulconbridge, 1959 (Box 224, Folder 19)
- Publications (Box 224, Folder 20)
- Statements from: Mr. Fred W. Creedle + H. Norton Sudduth (Box 224, Folder 21)
- Before the U.S. Senate Committee on Commerce Rebuttal Statement of H.E. Gilbert (Box 224, Folder 22)
- Interstate Commerce Commission: Rules Governing the Monthly Reports of Railroad Accidents, 1960 (Box 224, Folder 23)
- Memorandums, statements, affidavit, news releases, correspondence (Box 224, Folder 24)
- Agreement providing for protective conditions for employees (Box 224, Folder 25)
- Financing better transportation for the people of New York State, 1971 (Box 224, Folder 26)
- Ritual of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1920 (Box 224, Folder 27)
- Annual Dinner Programs, 1961-1968 (Box 224, Folder 13)
- Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1958 (Box 224, Folder 1)
- Publications - Includes National Railway Historical Society, Newsletters; "News Gram," 1950-58; and miscellaneous booklets and reports (Box 225, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated, B of L F & E - B of L E (Box 226, Folder 1)
  [not in box when re-boxed (8/17/2016)]
- Agreement - 6/25/64. Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers Conference (Box 226, Folder 2)
- Air-Brake Book - Rates, etc. Questions and answers (Box 226, Folder 3)
- Appeal of 1960. State Board Election (Box 226, Folder 4)
- Assessment Appeals 1964 (Box 226, Folder 5)
- Arbitration, Data compiled by H. E. Gilbert (Box 226, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (Box 226, Folder 7)
- Anti-Poverty Program and Economic Opportunity-Act of 1964 (Box 226, Folder 8)
- B of LF&E - Office of the President (Box 226, Folder 9)
- B of LF&E Time-book (Box 226, Folder 10)
- B of LF&E - B of RT 37 Point Program - Improved working conditions (Box 226, Folder 11)
- Brandon-Shearer & Flaherty - Attorneys (Box 226, Folder 12)
- B of LF&E - 1968 Convention (Box 226, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors (Box 226, Folder 14)
- By-laws - Pa. Leg. & Educ. Board - Amendments 1960 (Box 226, Folder 15)
- State BLF&E meeting (Box 226, Folder 16)
- BLE Propaganda (Box 226, Folder 17)
- BRT State meeting (Box 226, Folder 18)
- Beneficiary Dept. BLF&E (Box 226, Folder 19)
- BLF&E - Finance Comm. Reports (Box 226, Folder 20)
- BLF&E Headquarters Building (Box 226, Folder 21)
- BLF&E Minutes of State L&E Board meetings (Box 226, Folder 22)
- Colorado State Legislative Board (Box 226, Folder 23)
- Constitutions and by-laws (Box 226, Folder 24)
- Coal & Iron Police activities (Box 226, Folder 25)
- Child Labor (Box 226, Folder 26)
- Constitutions and by-laws (BLF&E) of other states (Box 226, Folder 27)
- Compulsory arbitration. Data compiled by H.E. Gilber (Box 226, Folder 28)
- Contrasts awarded by Penna. Railroad (Box 226, Folder 29)
- Canadian Legislative Board (Box 226, Folder 30)
- Central Labor Council (Box 226, Folder 31)
- Campaign- 1968 General Election (Box 226, Folder 32)
- Congressional records (Box 226, Folder 33)
- BLF&E "Diesel Manning Issue" (Box 226, Folder 34)
- Diesel-Electric Movement (Box 226, Folder 35)
- "Deadman" devices on all locomotives - PUC ruling (Box 226, Folder 36)
- Derailments and Wreck's In Penna. (Box 226, Folder 37)
- "Deaths" (Box 226, Folder 38)
- Drinking Water facilities (Box 226, Folder 39)
- Dynamic Brake Hearings (Box 226, Folder 40)
- Eugene V. Debs Foundation (Box 227, Folder 1)
- Election Laws of Pennsylvania (Box 227, Folder 2)
- Emergency R.R. Transportation Act (Box 227, Folder 2a)
- E.U.M.A. (Box 227, Folder 3)
- Executive Committee, 1959-1968 (Box 227, Folder 4)
- Earned Income, tax regulations (Box 227, Folder 5)
- Full Crew Hearing, Testimony of John W. Ludlow (Box 227, Folder 6)
- Full Crew Hearing. Testimony of William Miller (Box 227, Folder 7)
- Full Crew Law - Correspondence Penna. Law (Box 227, Folder 8)
- "Featherbedding" (Box 227, Folder 9)
- Federal Lavs - RR and Labor (Box 227, Folder 10)
- Full Crew Laws- Adms. of some in U.S. (Box 227, Folder 11)
- Full Train crews - Hearing before I.C.C. (Box 227, Folder 12)
- Full Crew Hearing, Testimony of J.H. Dreisback (Box 227, Folder 13)
- Full Crew Hearings, 1915-1917 (Box 227, Folder 14)
- Full Crew Hearings Harrisburg, 1938 (Box 227, Folder 15)
- Forty- four hour week. Laws-women's and general (Box 227, Folder 16)
- Federal Liability Act (Box 227, Folder 17)
- R. Fuller. Railway clerks (Box 227, Folder 18)
- General Policy Committee BLF&E (Box 227, Folder 19)
- General Transportation Situation (Box 227, Folder 20)
- Georgia State Legislative Board (Box 227, Folder 21)
- "Goods & Service a Installment Sales Act" (Box 227, Folder 22)
- Grand Lodge Employee's Strike (Box 227, Folder 23)
- Hours of Service Law (Box 227, Folder 24)
- Harris (Box 227, Folder 24a)
- I.C.C. Regulations on Transportation & Railroads (Box 227, Folder 25)
- Indiana State Legislative Board (Box 227, Folder 26)
- Iowa State Legislative Board (Box 227, Folder 27)
- Local Lodge Charters surrendered or revoked (Box 227, Folder 28)
- Lake Erie & Ohio River Waterway (Box 227, Folder 29)
- Lodge election results, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 30)
- Ladies Society. Correspondence (Box 227, Folder 31)
- Lobbying - Registration Act (Box 227, Folder 32)
- Legislature, 1965 (Box 227, Folder 33)
- Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Box 227, Folder 34)
- Local Tax Enabling Act no. 481 (Box 227, Folder 35)
- Labor Legislation in Pennsylvania (Box 227, Folder 36)
- Letters to the editor (Box 227, Folder 37)
- Legislature, 1966 (Box 227, Folder 38)
- Minimum Wage Law and Regulations (Box 228, Folder 1)
- Monthly reports (Box 228, Folder 2)
- Midland Yard. PUC Investigation (Box 228, Folder 3)
- Maryland State Legislative Board (Box 228, Folder 4)
- N.I.E.P. (Box 228, Folder 5)
- N.I.E.P. Second Phase (Box 228, Folder 6)
- New York State L & E Board (Box 228, Folder 7)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board. Cases pending (Box 228, Folder 8)
- New York State Full Crew Law - violations (Box 228, Folder 9)
- Newsletters. Five R.R. Brotherhoods (Box 228, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Labor Relations Act (Box 228, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania State Legislative Board Reports of General Assembly (Box 228, Folder 11a)
- Power or train Brake Law (Box 228, Folder 12)
- Passenger Service Improvement Corp, of Philadelphia. (Box 228, Folder 13)
- Railroad Lawsuits Against Management (Box 228, Folder 14)
- Railroad Accidents and Reports ICC Rules governing same (Box 228, Folder 15)
- Railway Labor's Political League (Box 228, Folder 16)
- Railroad Strikes (Box 228, Folder 17)
- Railroads - Unsanitary conditions & PUC Regulations for Railroads (Box 228, Folder 18)
- Railroads - Unsanitary conditions (Box 228, Folder 19)
- Railroad Retirement Reports (Box 228, Folder 20)
- Railroad Retirement Reports - OE-l&CT-l (Box 228, Folder 21)
- Railroad Consolidation Agreement (Box 228, Folder 22)
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance (Box 228, Folder 23)
- Railroad Retirement Correspondence 1934 (Box 228, Folder 24)
- Railroad Salaries (Box 228, Folder 25)
- Railways - Plant and Industrial - Regulations (Box 228, Folder 26)
- D.B. Robertson - Anniversary (Box 228, Folder 27)
- Raid on RR Retirement Board jobs - Schedule C Amendment (Box 228, Folder 28)
- Railroad Retirement SS numbers; Form G-88; OE-5&BA6 - Correspondence (Box 228, Folder 29)
- Railway Labor Act "Union Shops" (Box 228, Folder 30)
- Railroad Retirement Act, Board circulars and pamphlets (Box 228, Folder 31)
- Railroad clearance. P.U.C. order (Box 228, Folder 32)
- Railroad Workers Transportation by taxi and bus (Box 228, Folder 33)
- Railroad Retirement Act - General Correspondence (Box 229, Folder 1)
- Railway Political League - Penna. Division (Box 229, Folder 2)
- Rail Review and Report (Box 229, Folder 3)
- Railroad Laws (Box 229, Folder 4)
- Registration. (Box 229, Folder 5)
- Railroad Regulations. P.U.C. (Box 229, Folder 6)
- "Right to Work" Laws (Box 229, Folder 7)
- Railroad Accident Investigation ICC (Box 229, Folder 8)
- "Records of the Vote" Penna. General Assembly (Box 229, Folder 9)
- Railway Labor Act, Supreme Court Decision "Dues" used for politics (Box 229, Folder 10)
- Railroad Accidents (Box 229, Folder 11)
- Railway Labor's Political League (Box 229, Folder 12)
- Railway Labor's Political League, 1967 (Box 229, Folder 13)
- Railroad Safety Section - ICC injured RR Employees (Box 229, Folder 14)
- RLPL Funds for Penna. Conditions, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 15)
- Railroads Workers - newspaper clippings (Box 229, Folder 16)
- Safety awards R.R. (Box 229, Folder 17)
- Southern Union Meetings - Richmond, Va. (Box 229, Folder 18)
- St. Lawrence Waterway, Correspondence (Box 229, Folder 19)
- Stulton Highspire RR Crossing (Box 229, Folder 20)
- State Workmen's Insurance Fund (Box 229, Folder 21)
- Texas State Legislative Board (Box 229, Folder 22)
- Transportation and Labor (Box 229, Folder 23)
- Taft-Hartley Law, P.B.R.'s Interpretation (Box 229, Folder 24)
- Train Limit Hearing before ICC (Box 229, Folder 25)
- Trucks and buses (Box 229, Folder 26)
- Vacation agreement BLF&E (Box 229, Folder 27)
- Virginia State Legislative Board (Box 229, Folder 28)
- Vermont Legislative Board (Box 229, Folder 29)
- U.S. Savings and War Bonds (Box 229, Folder 30)
- Utah Legislative Board (Box 229, Folder 31)
- Women's Laws, State and Federal (Box 230, Folder 1)
- Workmen's Compensation, Lav and Correspondence (Box 230, Folder 2)
- Washington State Legislative Board (Box 230, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin State Legislative Board (Box 230, Folder 4)
- Wage Movement of Brotherhoods (Box 230, Folder 5)
- E.R. Wachof Dismissed from RR - Hostling Locomotive (Box 230, Folder 6)
- Yearly reports 1934-1941 inclusive (Box 230, Folder 7)
- Mergers - NYC-PRR (Box 230, Folder 8)
- PRR-NYC Merger. Circulars (Box 230, Folder 9)
- Merger - PRR-NYC, Newspaper clippings (Box 230, Folder 10)
- B&O-C&O - Merger (Box 230, Folder 11)
- Award - Arbitration Board no. 282 - Firemen (Helper) (Box 230, Folder 12)
- 555 - minutes of convention of BLF&E held Sept. 9-15 (Box 231, Folder 1)
- 1346 - minutes-reports of committees-addresses of speakers of convention, BLF&E, Sept. 1932 (Box 231, Folder 2)
- Information on the Firemen, notes. Write Congressmen and Senators (Box 231, Folder 3)
- Legislative - notes on our meeting-1963, 1960 Committees appointed (Box 231, Folder 4)
- Important, Legislative Letters - T.F. Purnell - Notes on meeting (Box 231, Folder 5)
- Record of voting 1965 General Assembly (Box 231, Folder 6)
- Legislative Board meeting, Board of Directors, meeting, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  May 1963 - Information appointment committee
- Penna. State Legislative and Education Board, BLF&E Reports (Box 231, Folder 8)
- Penna. State Legislative & Education Board, 1965 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  Legislation News
- Penna. State Legislative & Education Board (Box 231, Folder 10)
  Monthly Reports
- Penna. State Legislative & Education Board, 1968 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  Unification, BLF&E Field Staff meeting
- Penna. State Legislative & Education Board, 1967 (Box 231, Folder 12)
- Abandonment of Trains (Box 231, Folder 13)
- B&O A. 79924 Connellsville & Grafton, W. Va., Trains 65 & 66 (Box 231, Folder 14)
- B&O A. 82195, Pittsburgh & Buffalo, Trains 251 & 252 (Box 231, Folder 15)
- B&O A. 82384, Pittsburgh & Claysville, Trains 233-738, 72-238 (Box 231, Folder 16)
- B&O A. 81985, Galeton, Pa, & N.Y. State Line (Box 231, Folder 17)
- B&Q A. 84980, Chester & Wayne Jac, Philadelphia (Box 231, Folder 18)
- B&O RR Dropping of Two Trains in Lawrence Co. (Box 231, Folder 19)
- B&O F.D. 22201, Discontinuance of Trains 21 & 22 - Baltimore, Washington & Pittsburgh (Box 231, Folder 20)
- B&O RR A. 94645, Abandonment of passenger Trains, #8 & 9 - Lawrence Co (Box 231, Folder 21)
- B&LE A. 78003, No. Bessemer & Greenville Trains 1 & 2 (Box 231, Folder 22)
- B&LE A. 81451, Greenville & Erie, Trains 12 & 13 (Box 231, Folder 23)
- B&LE F.D. 21038, Abandonment of Indionola Branch Line (Box 231, Folder 24)
- CRR of N.J. A. 80767, Scranton Station (Box 231, Folder 25)
- CRR of N.J. A. 89072, Jim Thorpe-Wilkes-Barre 301-306 (Box 231, Folder 26)
- CRR of N.J. A. 93783, Allentown and New York (Box 231, Folder 27)
- CRR of Pa. A. 77982, MauchChunk and Allentown Trains 1078, 1107-104 & 1104 (Box 231, Folder 28)
- D&H C.15080, Carbondale and Scranton Trains 505, 509, 508 and 512 (Box 231, Folder 29)
- DL&W FD. 20684, Hoboken and Scranton Trains, 11&26-28 (Box 231, Folder 30)
- DL&W F.D. 20727, Scranton to Binghamton (Box 231, Folder 31)
- DS Railroad A. 90436, Abandonment of its Line, Donora and Carroll township (Box 231, Folder 32)
- H&BT A. 80310, EBT A. 8l64l, EBT A. 82774 (Box 231, Folder 33)
- E&MRR A. 87812, Abandonment of line in Etna, Allegheny (Box 231, Folder 34)
- E-LRR F.D. 23045, Discontinuance of train #44-Scranton & Hoboken (Box 231, Folder 35)
- Erie A. 79702, Port Jarvis & Binghamton trains 27 & 28 (Box 231, Folder 36)
- Erie, Gang Mills to Newberry Station (Box 231, Folder 37)
- E-LRR Discontinuance of Passenger train #45, Hoboken, N.J. and Scranton (Box 231, Folder 38)
- E-LRR F.D. 22551-52, Discontinuance of Trains 40-41-43 & 25-26 (Box 231, Folder 39)
- E-LRR F.D. 24886, Abandonment of Passenger trains 15 & 10, Buffalo, N.Y. & Hoboken, N.J. (Box 231, Folder 40)
- LV Hazleton and Lehighton (Box 231, Folder 41)
- LY I.D. 47, Adequacy of Passenger train service in Penna. (Box 231, Folder 42)
- LY A. 86035, Hazleton and Lehighton (Box 231, Folder 43)
- LV F.D. 20443, Passenger Service in Penna. (Box 231, Folder 44)
- LV F.D, 20824, Hazleton & Lehighton Trains 229, 228, 239 and 207 (Box 231, Folder 45)
- LV F.D. 21260, N.Y.C, Buffalo, N.Y. & Lehighton (Box 231, Folder 46)
- LV I.C.C. F.D. 24190-24l-91-92 & 93, Abandonment of Montrose (Box 231, Folder 47)
- L&NE Abandonment (Box 231, Folder 48)
- M&P A. 81318, York-Pa -Md, boundary (Box 231, Folder 49)
- Mononghela C.D. 6651, Ry. Size of crew (Box 231, Folder 50)
- Mon. A. 85927, Freight Service (Box 231, Folder 51)
- NYC A. 87574, Abandonment of passenger service and its station, North East, Erie Co. (Box 231, Folder 52)
- NYC, Cleveland-Buffalo-trains 50 & 289 (Box 231, Folder 53)
- PRR, Pittsburgh and Buffalo trains (Box 231, Folder 54)
- PRR 45754, Illinois-Missouri State Line, train 6 (Box 231, Folder 55)
- PRR A. 75795, Beaver Falls & Sharon, trains 404 & 405 (Box 231, Folder 56)
- PRR A. 77863, Oil City and Corry trains 980 & 981 (Box 231, Folder 57)
- PRR A. 77939, Allen Lane, Philadelphia. & White Marsh trains, 804, 813, 856 & 863 (Box 231, Folder 58)
- PRR A. 77956, Greencastle & Harrisburgh trains 640 & 6 (Box 231, Folder 59)
- PRR A. 78108, Pittsburgh & Washington, Pa. trains 763 & 760 (Box 231, Folder 60)
- PRR A. 78915, Lancaster & York (Box 231, Folder 61)
- PRR A. 79046, Pittsburgh & Brownsville trains 8lO & 807 (Box 231, Folder 62)
- PRR A. 79112, Manayunk & Norristown (Box 231, Folder 63)
- PRR A. 80059, Elroma & Brownsville, trains 807 & 810 (Box 231, Folder 64)
- PRR A. 80620, Pittsburgh & East Brady, trains 913 & 9l4 (Box 231, Folder 65)
- PRR A. 81084, Derry & Pittsburgh, trains 631, 644, 512 and 513, 519 (Box 231, Folder 66)
- PRR A. 82396, Williamsport & Harrisburg, trains 525, 526, 527 (Box 231, Folder 67)
- PRR A. 82521, Kiskiminetas Jet & East Brady, trains 913 & 914 (Box 231, Folder 68)
- PRR A. 82622, Williamsport & Troy, N.Y. trains 595, 596 & 598 (Box 231, Folder 69)
- PRR A. 85491, A.85641, Pittsburgh & Beaver Falls, train363-64 & 65 (Box 231, Folder 70)
- PRR A. 85497, Harrisburgh-Williamsport trains 528, 529 (Box 231, Folder 71)
- PRR A. 85815, Media & West Chester, trains 0765 & 0768 (Box 231, Folder 72)
- PRR A. 86220, Phila-Pittsburgh curtailment of service (Box 231, Folder 73)
- PRR A. 86875, Aladdin & Pittsburgh, trains 922 & 923 (Box 231, Folder 74)
- PRR Erie trains 580 & 58l (Box 231, Folder 75)
- PRR A. 87361, Abandonment of trains, 26 - Pittsburgh (Box 231, Folder 76)
- PRR A. 87587, Manayunk-Phila. (Box 231, Folder 77)
- PRR F.D. 21936, A. 87818, Abandonment of Cumberland. Valley Branch (Box 231, Folder 78)
- PRR A. 87911, Hbg.-Phila, trains 602&607 (Box 231, Folder 79)
- PRR A. 87945, Hbg.-Phila trains 603-604 (Box 231, Folder 80)
- PRR F.D, 21986, Buffalo-New York-Hbg. trains 570-576-572-571-573 (Box 231, Folder 81)
- F.D. 18418, PRR, Jersey City & Brooklyn. (Box 232, Folder 1)
- PRR, F.D. 20792, Harrisburg &. Williamsport nos, 528 & 529 (Box 232, Folder 2)
- PRR F. D.21589, Discontinuance of Pittsburgh Suburban Lines (Box 232, Folder 3)
- PRR A. 89906, Trains 807 & 8l0, Pittsburgh-Elrama (Box 232, Folder 4)
- PRR F.D. 21589, A. 87747, Pittsburgh Suburban trains (Box 232, Folder 5)
- PRR F.D, 21840, A. 88091, 90434 Trains 39-37 and 635 Phila. to Pittsburgh and Phila. to Harrisburg (Box 232, Folder 6)
- PRR F.D. 24398 trains 570-571, Buffalo, NY and Baltimore (Box 232, Folder 7)
- PRR A. 90700, Abandonment of Suburban Service in Pittsburgh area (Box 232, Folder 8)
- PRR I.D. 48, Curtailment of Passenger Service -Washington, D. C., Pittsburgh, Phila. and New York (Box 232, Folder 9)
- PER A. 91401, Discontinuance of passenger trains nos. 580 & 58l - Erie & Emporium (Box 232, Folder 10)
- PRR A. 94l67, Trains nos. 28 & 29 Broadway Ltd, and General (Box 232, Folder 11)
- P&LE A. 89204, Trains nos. 277 & 280 Pittsburgh and New Castle (Box 232, Folder 12)
- P&LE A.90124 Trains nos. 274-273 New Castle, Pittsburgh, Beaver Falls (Box 232, Folder 13)
- P.&LE, A. 93459 (Box 232, Folder 14)
- Penn Central A. 94464 (Box 232, Folder 15)
- Penn Central F.D. 25026 (Box 232, Folder 16)
- Penn Central F.D. 25308 (Box 232, Folder 17)
- Penn Central F.D. 25074 (Box 232, Folder 18)
- Penn Central F.D. 25373 (Box 232, Folder 19)
- Penn Central I&SD 8486 (Box 232, Folder 20)
- Penn Central F.D. 24972, F.D. 25028 (Box 232, Folder 21)
- Penn Central A. 94464 (Box 232, Folder 22)
- Reading A. 81651 (Box 232, Folder 23)
- Reading A. 82817 (Box 232, Folder 24)
- Reading A. 85012 (Box 232, Folder 25)
- Reading A. 85803 (Box 232, Folder 26)
- Reading A. 86503 (Box 232, Folder 27)
- P&LE A. 85626 (Box 232, Folder 28)
- P&LE A. 85765 (Box 232, Folder 29)
- Beading A. 86486 (Box 232, Folder 30)
- Reading A. 86596 (Box 232, Folder 31)
- Reading A, 86818 (Box 232, Folder 32)
- Reading A. 87051, F.D. 21274 (Box 232, Folder 33)
- Reading A. 87195 (Box 232, Folder 34)
- Reading A. 87483 (Box 232, Folder 35)
- Reading A. 88645, A88646 (Box 232, Folder 36)
- Reading A. 88641, 88642, 88643, 88644 (Box 232, Folder 37)
- Reading A. 91510 (Box 232, Folder 38)
- Reading A. 91551 (Box 232, Folder 39)
- Reading A. 91532 (Box 232, Folder 40)
- Reading I.D. 70 (Box 232, Folder 41)
- Change in status of stations, crossings, unsafe working conditions, walkways, etc. (Box 232, Folder 42-45)
- Change in status of stations, crossings, unsafe working conditions, walkways, etc. (Box 233, Folder 1-24)
- Mergers (Box 233, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous railroads (Box 233, Folder 26)
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 233, Folder 27)
- Bessemert & Lake Erie RR (Box 233, Folder 28)
- Cambria & Indiana RR (Box 233, Folder 29)
- Central RR of N.J. (Box 233, Folder 30)
- Delaware and Hudson RR (Box 233, Folder 31)
- Erie-Lackawanna RR (Box 233, Folder 32)
- Lehigh & New England RR F.D. 25215 (Box 233, Folder 33)
- Lehigh Valley RR (Box 233, Folder 34)
- Monongahela Comm. RR (Box 233, Folder 35)
- Monongahela Railway (Box 233, Folder 36)